distinct duplicated titles: 4697
rows involved: 10333

count distribution:
count
2     4178
3      390
4       70
5       26
6        9
7        7
8        4
9        2
10       1
11       2
Name: count, dtype: int64

--- 1. [2x] labels=[2, 2] 'KPMG to Pay \\$10 Million to Settle Charges Over Gemstar Audits'
    KPMG LLP yesterday agreed to pay \$10 million to settle Securities and Exchange Commission charges that the fi
     KPMG LLP yesterday agreed to pay \$10 million to settle Securities and Exchange Commission charges that the f

--- 2. [2x] labels=[3, 3] 'Online fraud: We got law, but no enforcement'
    Plenty of laws exist to prosecute online identity thieves and fraudsters, and also to co-opt ISPs (Internet Se
    Because of the open nature of the Internet, there seems to be no immediate prospects that technology or law en

--- 3. [2x] labels=[1, 1] 'NBA Wrap: Nowitzki Leads Dallas Past Minnesota'
     NEW YORK (Reuters) - Dirk Nowitzki scored 34 points as the  Dallas Mavericks beat the Minnesota Timberwolves 
    Dirk Nowitzki scored 34 points as the Dallas Mavericks beat the Minnesota Timberwolves 97-87 in National Baske

--- 4. [2x] labels=[2, 3] 'Netflix Girds for DVD Rental Price War'
    The future suddenly looks shaky for online DVD rental pioneer Netflix Inc. - a plucky home entertainment upsta
    The future suddenly looks shaky for online DVD rental pioneer Netflix Inc. - a plucky home entertainment upsta

--- 5. [2x] labels=[2, 2] 'Eli Lilly Bares All'
    Given recent furor regarding clinical trials of pharmaceuticals, Eli Lilly (NYSE: LLY) has unveiled a Web site
    In the spirit of full disclosure, the Big Pharma company publishes clinical trial results online.

--- 6. [2x] labels=[2, 2] 'Wells Fargo, U.S. Bancorp Profits Rise'
     NEW YORK (Reuters) - Wells Fargo   Co. &lt;A HREF="http://www.investor.reuters.com/FullQuote.aspx?ticker=WFC.
     NEW YORK (Reuters) - Wells Fargo   Co. &lt;A HREF="http://www.investor.reuters.com/FullQuote.aspx?ticker=WFC.

--- 7. [2x] labels=[2, 2] 'Consumer Spending Was Flat in August'
    Consumer spending was flat in August even though incomes rose, the Commerce Department reported yesterday, pro
    Consumer spending was flat in August even though incomes rose, the Commerce Department reported yesterday, pro

--- 8. [2x] labels=[0, 0] 'Large Explosion Kills Eight in Baghdad'
    BAGHDAD, Iraq - A large explosion hit outside a police academy in downtown Baghdad on Sunday, killing eight pe
    BAGHDAD, Iraq - A large explosion hit outside a police academy in downtown Baghdad on Sunday, killing eight pe

--- 9. [2x] labels=[2, 2] 'Toyota Prius Voted European Car of Year'
     TOKYO (Reuters) - Toyota Motor Corp.'s Prius hybrid has  been voted 2005 European Car of the Year, Japan's to
    Toyota Motor Corp. #39;s Prius hybrid has been voted 2005 European Car of the Year, Japan #39;s top auto maker

--- 10. [2x] labels=[3, 3] 'Hollywood majors back Toshiba DVD'
    Toshiba Corp says it has won support for the HD DVD optical disc standard from Warner Bros Studios, Paramount 
    Toshiba said on Monday that four major Hollywood studios had thrown their crucial weight behind High Definitio

--- 11. [2x] labels=[2, 2] 'Oil Hits Record on China, India Demand'
    LONDON (Reuters) - Oil prices struck a fresh record high above \$47 a barrel on Thursday as fresh evidence of 
     LONDON (Reuters) - Oil prices struck a fresh record high  above \$47.50 a barrel on Thursday as fresh evidenc

--- 12. [3x] labels=[2, 2, 2] 'Etiquette at Work'
    Q: Through downsizing, attrition, and layoffs, I'm the only English-speaking person left on my team. My two re
    Q: What are the rules regarding hand shakes in business situations? Should men stand when shaking hands with e

--- 13. [2x] labels=[2, 3] 'Is It Still Called a Venture Fund When You Use Your Own Money?'
    Halsey M. Minor, the former CNET guru, is now running his own, very private, investment fund.
    Halsey M. Minor, the founder of CNET, is now running his own, very private, investment fund.

--- 14. [2x] labels=[1, 1] 'American League Game Summary - New York at Toronto'
    Hudson #39;s homer was 10th of the season...The Blue Jays are 31-32 as the host this season, while the Yankees
    Matsui had made 1,251 consecutive starts with the Yomiuri Giants in his native Japan and has played in all 322

--- 15. [2x] labels=[2, 2] 'Oil Above \\$47 After New Record'
     SINGAPORE (Reuters) - Oil prices struck another record high  on Thursday and remained supported above \$47 by
    SINGAPORE (Reuters) - Oil prices struck another record high on Thursday and remained supported above \$47 by a

--- 16. [2x] labels=[0, 0] 'Bombings, Gun Attacks in India Kill 44'
    GAUHATI, India - A spate of bombings and gun attacks in crowded public places killed 44 people Saturday in mar
    GAUHATI, India - In a shattering series of attacks, suspected separatists hit nine targets - a railroad statio

--- 17. [2x] labels=[3, 3] 'Yahoo buys e-mail search company'
    com October 21, 2004, 6:42 PM PT. This priority retains its ranking at number five as more and more companies 
    Yahoo Inc., one of the largest online based companies said, it has bought out privately held e-mail search fir

--- 18. [2x] labels=[3, 3] 'Bush signs extension to R D tax credit'
    The R D tax credit, first passed as a temporary measure in 1981, has been extended 11 times and allows U.S. co
    WASHINGTON - U.S. President George Bush on Monday signed a bill that included an 18 month extension of a resea

--- 19. [2x] labels=[0, 1] 'Woods Marries Model in Barbados Ceremony'
    SANDY LANE BEACH, Barbados - Tiger Woods married Swedish model Elin Nordegren at an exclusive resort in Barbad
    Tiger Woods married Swedish model Elin Nordegren at an exclusive resort in Barbados during a sunset ceremony t

--- 20. [2x] labels=[2, 2] 'Disney Chief to Leave, Setting Off Race for Job'
    Michael D. Eisner, who has spent much of the last year fending off challenges to his two-decade reign at the W
    Michael Eisner announced an exit on his own terms, shifting the spotlight from the debate over his leadership 

--- 21. [2x] labels=[0, 0] 'Teams Scour Indonesia Plane Crash Site for Survivors'
     SOLO, Indonesia (Reuters) - Rescue teams searched areas  around an airfield in central Indonesia on Wednesday
     SOLO, Indonesia (Reuters) - Rescue teams searched areas  around a central Indonesia airport Wednesday for sur

--- 22. [2x] labels=[2, 3] 'Infineon to plead guilty in memory chip case'
    Germany #39;s Infineon Technologies AG has agreed to plead guilty to charges of price-fixing and pay a \$160 m
    Becomes the first company to plead guilty to conspiring with manufacturers to fix the prices of DRAM chips in 

--- 23. [2x] labels=[2, 2] 'Philips to Reduce Value of Stake in MedQuist'
    Philips Electronics said on Wednesday that it would take a \$752 million charge in the fourth quarter to reduc
    Royal Philips Electronics said on Wednesday that it would take a \$752 million charge in the fourth quarter to

--- 24. [2x] labels=[2, 2] 'Amazon Posts Profit, Outlook Disappoints (Reuters)'
    Reuters - Amazon.com Inc.  on\Thursday posted quarterly earnings that more than tripled on\strong internationa
    Reuters - Amazon.com Inc.  on\Thursday posted quarterly earnings that more than tripled on\strong internationa

--- 25. [3x] labels=[1, 1, 1] 'English Premier League match reports'
    Champions Arsenal dropped their first points of the season when a late Henrik Pedersen equaliser earned Bolton
    Graeme Souness got off to a winning Premier League start as Newcastle claimed their first away league victory 

--- 26. [2x] labels=[1, 1] 'Syracuse, Off to a Fast Start, Wins Tournament'
    Facing two Top 25 teams in two nights in the Coaches vs. Cancer Classic, the Orange handled both with relative
    The season may be young, but No. 6 Syracuse has already made a statement. Facing two Top 25 teams in two night

--- 27. [2x] labels=[2, 2] 'Kuwait Backs Quota Hike if Prices Stay Up'
     ABU DHABI (Reuters) - Major Gulf oil producer Kuwait will  back a hike of 1 million barrels per day in OPEC's
    Major Gulf oil producer Kuwait will back a hike of 1 million barrels per day in OPEC #39;s output ceiling if c

--- 28. [3x] labels=[3, 3, 3] 'ICANN enters negotiations on .mobi, .jobs domains'
    Two new top-level domain names moved closer to approval this week, as the body charged with overseeing the Int
    ICANN has begun commercial and technical negotiations with the applicant registries, bringing the number of do

--- 29. [2x] labels=[0, 0] 'Israel releases senior Hamas leader'
    A senior member of the Palestinian resistance group Hamas has been released from an Israeli prison after compl
    A senior leader of the Islamic Resistance Movement (Hamas) in the West Bank was released after two years of de

--- 30. [2x] labels=[0, 1] 'Rockets Nip Kings As NBA Travels to China'
    SHANGHAI, China - Hometown hero Yao Ming scored 14 points to lead the Houston Rockets to an 88-86 win over the
    The crowd chanted Yao Ming's name all game, soaking up the novelty of the NBA in another tribute to a player w

--- 31. [2x] labels=[0, 1] 'Henman Falls to Novak in Basel'
     BASEL, Switzerland (Reuters) - British world number four  Tim Henman was knocked out of the quarterfinals of 
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; By Mark Ledsom&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; BASEL, Switzerland (Reuters) - British world nu

--- 32. [2x] labels=[2, 2] 'Fed: Economic Growth on Track'
     WASHINGTON (Reuters) - U.S. economic expansion remains on  track and inflation under control, top Federal Res
    US economic expansion remains on track and inflation under control, top Federal Reserve officials said Wednesd

--- 33. [3x] labels=[0, 0, 0] 'Body Resembling Japanese Hostage Found in Iraq'
     TOKYO (Reuters) - A body resembling a Japanese hostage has  been found in Iraq and is being shipped to Qatar 
     TOKYO (Reuters) - A body resembling a Japanese hostage has  been found in Iraq and is being shipped to Qatar 

--- 34. [2x] labels=[2, 2] 'PeopleSoft Ousts CEO Who Battled Oracle'
     In NEW YORK story headlined "PeopleSoft ousts CEO amid  battle with Oracle," please read in paragraph 5, "Ora
    Oct. 1, 2004 - In NEW YORK story headlined  quot;PeopleSoft ousts CEO amid battle with Oracle, quot; please re

--- 35. [2x] labels=[0, 0] 'India test-fires nuclear-capable ballistic missile (AFP)'
    AFP - India has successfully tested a naval version of its Prithvi-III nuclear-capable medium range ballistic 
    AFP - India has successfully tested a naval version of its Prithvi-III nuclear-capable medium range ballistic 

--- 36. [2x] labels=[0, 0] 'Kerry Decries Bush Plan to Recall Troops'
    CINCINNATI - John Kerry, telling fellow combat veterans he's their "true brother in arms," said Wednesday that
    CINCINNATI - Democratic presidential candidate John Kerry on Wednesday criticized President Bush's proposal to

--- 37. [2x] labels=[1, 1] 'Thursday #39;s Golf Capsules'
    Stewart Cink made five birdies on his first 10 holes and led by one shot over Rod Pampling before the rain-del
    Corey Pavin sank seven birdies and matched his career low with an 8-under-par 62 for a three-stroke lead at th

--- 38. [2x] labels=[2, 3] 'AOL Enters the Online Travel Market'
    New service will compete with sites like Travelocity.com and Expedia.
    America Online is aiming to get a piece of the travel search market, announcing plans to introduce a new Web-b

--- 39. [2x] labels=[2, 2] "McDonald's: CEO Resting After New Surgery"
     WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The chief executive of McDonald's  Corp. &lt;A HREF="http://www.investor.reuters.com/F
     WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The chief executive of McDonald's  Corp. is recuperating after another surgery, the wo

--- 40. [2x] labels=[3, 3] 'SpaceShipOne Wins Ten-Million-Dollar X Prize'
    Brian Binnie, a veteran US Navy aviator and one of four pilots trained to fly SpaceShipOne, piloted the spacec
    SpaceShipOne, the world's first privately built manned spacecraft, completed its third round-trip journey to s
